- Земля.
Огонь.
Воздух.
Вода.
Только аватар может овладеть всеми 4-мя стихиями
и поддерживать гармонию в этом мире.
- Кувира угрожает взять Заофу силой.
Между Су Бейфонг и её бывшей ученицей
вспыхнула вражда, и Корра вызвалась заключить перемирие.
Но было уже слишком поздно.
Су со воими сыновьями уже были на пути
к лагерю Кувиры, чтобы убить её.
В то же время, Болин и Варрик узнали о
тиранических намерениях Кувиры и сбежали из её армии.
Но их поймали и теперь держат в неволе,
а Жюли предала Варрика и теперь служит Кувире.
- Ты уверена, что это сработает?
Даже без Кувиры, они способны нас сокрушить.
- БОльшую часть этой армии заставили
служить Кувире.
Если мы уберём её с дороги, у них не будет причин сражаться.
Сегодня мы положим конец правлению тирана.
Она там одна.
Это наш шанс.
- Не бейте меня!
- Жюли?
- Я знала, что ты попытаешься незаметно напасть.
Ты боялась брать ответственность в управлении Царством земли,
когда у тебя был шанс, ты боялась присоединиться ко мне,
когда я стала лидером,
а сейчас ты боишься честного сражения.
Ты всегда была трусом.
Взять их.
- Корра, ты должна остановить Су,
пока она не совершит непоправимое.
- Остановить её? Да мы должны помогать ей!
- Мы понятия не имеем, где сейчас твоя мама, или какой у неё план.
Если мы ворвёмся в лагерь Кувиры,
их всех заберут в плен, если не хуже.
Всё, что мы сейчас можем - это ждать.
- Внимание, граждане Заофу.
Ваш лидер, Су Бейфонг, попыталась напасть на меня
сегодня ночью, пока я спала, игнорируя условия нашего перемирия.
К счастью, сейчас она со своей штурмовой группой находится у меня под стражей.
- Нет.
- Тем не менее, будьте уверены, я не буду мстить
мирному населению Заофу,
если ваши оставшиеся представители
встретятся со мной у ворот на рассвете, чтобы предложить
полную и безоговорчную капитуляцию.
На этом всё.
- Корра, ты не можешь дать Кувире сойти это с рук.
Мы должны вырвать моих братьев и маму из плена.
- Ты дала клятву о поддержании мира
когда стала магом воздуха.
Ты не можешь просто взять и напасть на Кувиру.
- Да плевать мне на эту клятву.
Я должна спасти свою семью.
- Нет, Джинора права.
Твоя мама напала на лагерь.
Кувира просто защищала себя.
- Защищала себя?
Она хотела напасть на наш город!
Не могу поверить, что ты отказываешься сражаться.
- Почему эта дамочка из громкоговорителя глаголит,
когда я пытаюсь уснуть?
- Корра, что же нам делать?
- Я и Джинора пойдём поговорим с Кувирой на рассвете,
и, может быть, мы сможем как-нибудь договориться.
Обещаю, я сделаю всё, чтобы сохранить мир.
- Я пойду с тобой.
- Мы тоже пойдём.
- Нет.
Папа попросил нас найти Корру, и мы её нашли.
А сейчас вам надо держаться в безопасности.
- Да ладно тебе, дай нам помочь.
- Я не хочу, чтобы они могли схватить кого-то ещё.
Вы можете остаться с Батаром и Хуаном,
пока я разбираюсь с Кувирой.
Убедитесь, чтобы они вернулись к Тензину,
Если что-то пойдёт не так.
- Вот, блин.
Когда я наконец увижу драку?
- Банка для печенья пуста.
Нет горячих полотенец.
Никто не чистит мне уши..
Жюли!
Эх, её и впрямь нет.
- Вставай и за дело, Варрик. Пора работать.
Мы оборудовали для тебя новую лабораторию.
Кувира хочет получить исправное оружие на лозе духов
как можно быстрее.
- Жюли всегда встречала меня утром
с чашкой горячего чая в руках.
- Ты получишь свой чай, когда начнёшь работать.
- Ну, я, вообще говоря, продуктивен
только где-то 15 минут в день,
Обычно - днём, около 15:45.
- Ты будешь работать прямо сейчас.
Я хочу, чтобы ты показал мне, как работает это устройство.
- Что происходит?
- Спи давай. Нам нужен только Варрик.
Тебе понадобится энергия, когда ты доберёшься до исправительного лагеря.
- I can't be expected
to work without an assistant.
Without zhu li,
I'm helpless.
- One of the guards
will be your assistant.
I'll be supervising.
- Well, I guess he'll be fine,
As long as he doesn't
need his hands afterwards.
- What's he talking about, sir?
- The last time we worked
with the spirit vines,
It created
an uncontrollable blast
That burned through a wall
and could still be
Blowing up comets in space,
as far as I know.
I wouldn't want to assist me
if I were you.
- Maybe we should just
let the kid help him out.
- Fine.
Bolin can assist.
- Wait, what? I need my hands!
Uh, hold on.
Can we get breakfast first?
While we still have hands?
- Release them now!
- If su agrees to bow to me
and turn over zaofu,
She and the rest of your family
will not be harmed.
- Never!
I'll never bow to you!
- There must be some way
for us to resolve this.
- I've already laid out
my terms,
And I think
they're very reasonable.
After all, su did try
to take me out
During
our peaceful negotiations.
- You call bringing an army
to threaten our city peaceful?
- Where's bolin?
I know he would never
go along with this!
- Bolin is with my fiance,
Working on something
very important,
But I assure you
he's on board with my plans.
You two have been apart
for some time.
I guess you don't realize
how much bolin has grown up.
Now turn over zaofu.
- I can't just let you
take the city.
- Avatar korra,
you are interfering
With internal earth empire
business
And letting
your personal feelings
Get in the way of reason.
Zaofu cannot
continue to rule itself.
They have been hoarding
their riches
And technology too long.
I'm here to distribute
those resources fairly
Throughout the nation.
This is about equality.
- You don't care about equality!
This is about control!
Just take her down.
You know
it's the right thing to do.
You have to stop this!
- The only way you're going
to keep me from marching
Into zaofu
is if you physically stop me.
Now what are you going to do?
- It looks like
you're not giving me a choice.
- Fine.
I want you all to know
that I would never
Ask any of you to do something
That I'm not willing
to do myself.
So rather than risk your lives,
I will fight the avatar
one-on-one.
Korra, if you win,
Then you can do
whatever you want with zaofu.
But after I beat you,
I want you out of my business
for good.
I'm the one who brought peace
to the earth empire, not you.
You're not relevant here
anymore.
- Fine.
You want to fight the avatar?
Then let's finish this
right here, right now!
- Are you really ready
to fight her?
- Just stay back
and let me handle this.
It's been a while,
But I got
a lot of pent-up rage.
- Don't mess around.
Kuvira is too good.
Just go into the avatar state
and get it over with.
- No, I'm only going
to use that as a last resort.
- Be careful.
- Use whatever you want,
all the elements,
The avatar state,
anything you need.
I know you're a little rusty.
- Хватит болтать.
- Looks like the avatar
is a little off her game.
- Don't let her
get you frustrated!
She wants you
to make a mistake!
- Болин, сделай это.
- Что "это"?
- Ну ЭТО!
Мне никогда не приходилось говорить Жюли, что значит "это"!
- А я не Жюли, ясно?
Pretend I don't know anything
About anything
that's happening here.
Also pretend I don't want
to build a super weapon
Or get my hands blown off.
- Walk me through
what you're doing.
I want to know
every detail of your work.
- You know, when I started
working with the vines,
The point was to find a clean,
unlimited source of energy,
Not develop
some spirity death ray.
- Clean energy,
sounds great!
Who doesn't like that stuff?
Let's do that instead.
- Quiet.
You're here to help, not talk.
And you of all people
should realize
That once a discovery is made,
It is our responsibility
as scientists
To pursue it as far as we can,
wherever it leads.
- How would you know?
You couldn't discover
a wolf-bat
If it was building a nest
in your butt.
- ooh.
- You're pathetic.
Wolf-bats don't build nests.
- Ooh, you got me there,
dr. Science.
You'll never know how it feels
to give birth to genius,
Only to have it kidnapped
and raised by fools.
- Are you done
with your rambling,
Or do the guards
need to encourage you
To continue your work?
- Okay, okay, okay.
The last time we ran
the current through the vine,
We couldn't control the power.
So I'm trying something new
to see if I can direct it.
- Come on, avatar.
Get up.
Show me what you've got.
- We have to help her.
- No.
Stay back.
I can handle this.
- So I see how the current
interacts with the vine,
And here is
a kind of directional tube,
But this baffling
here at the base...
- It looks like that would
only redirect the energy
Right back where it came from.
And what's that piece of
equipment you're fiddling with
Now on the power source?
- Hand me
the screw-turn-thingy, would ya?
- Ugh, I can't believe
you're helping them.
You know this isn't right.
- Funny story, bolin.
I first got the idea
for harnessing spirit power
When I watched
that giant unalaq monster
Attack the city
from my jail cell.
That giant monster
set me free.
Trust me, kid.
I know what I'm doing.
[grunts]
that ought to do it.
Huh.
Okay, stand back.
[device beeping]
there we go.
- What's that ticking?
- That's the timer.
- The timer for what?
- For the bomb, of course!
- What?
What bomb?
- The bomb that's going
to explode in five minutes
And destroy this entire train,
all of the spirit vines,
And everything else
within a few hundred yards.
You know what, I'd get
out of here if I were you.
This is the first time
I've built a timer,
And it might run
a little fast.
Bolin and I are ready
to go down with the ship--
Or train in this case--
But you seem like
you have a lot to live for.
- No, no, no, no!
I'm not ready to go down
with the ship or the train!
- You're bluffing.
- Stick around five minutes,
And you'll find out
who's bluffing.
You'll be sorry you left me,
zhu li!
When they write
the history books,
Your name will be
synonymous with betrayal!
People will say, "hey,
what happened to that guy?"
"oh, didn't you hear,
He varrick'd himself
because some girl zhu li'd him!"
- Enough.
- [whimpers]
- What makes you think
we'd let you blow yourself up?
You're working for kuvira.
You don't get to quit.
Grab him.
- You try to pull me away
from this thing,
And I'll hit this remote
and blow it immediately.
- Why do you have
a timer and a remote?
- Well, first I built the timer,
but then I thought
You could drag me off the train,
so then I built a remote.
But then I thought,
"well, now,
"do I really need
the timer anymore?
Because I got a remote
in my"--
Whatever!
I'm covering all my bases!
The point is, you're leaving.
We're staying.
- You have to go
into the avatar state!
Do it!
- I don't understand.
We got the poison out.
What's wrong with her?
- I knew you were weak.
You broke our agreement!
Attack!
- Keep them back!
I'm calling for help.
- Stunning work, ikki.
It hurts my eyes
with its raw emotional power.
Ah, pedestrian.
I already know what you
look like on the outside.
I want you to show me
the inner meelo.
- Help!
You have to get korra
and the rest of us
Out of here now!
Hurry!
- Finally!
Let's get it on!
- This is everyone.
Our half of the train is clear.
- That's good.
We're almost out of time.
- You're insane.
- You knew that
when you hired me.
Bolin, do the thing.
- Uh...
- Unhook the cars!
Oh, come on,
that was an easy one!
- Man, that was great.
I gotta admit, you had me
going there for a while.
I really thought
you were going to blow us up.
Now, how do we
turn this thing off?
- Oh, we can't turn it off.
We're going to blow up.
But we had a pretty good run,
right?
- What are you talking about,
a good run?
I'm still running!
I like running!
- I'll see you
on the other side, zhu li.
- I want you to know,
I hate you.
- I can't believe
he actually blew himself up.
That man was crazier
than a sewer-pipe elephant rat.
Let's get back to zaofu.
[both coughing]
Yes!
You did it, bolin.
You did the thing.
Mwah!
- I can't believe
Zhu li worked for you
as long as she did.
- Dive, pepper!
Dive!
Here comes a hurricane!
You can't handle
all this meelo!
- We've got her!
Go!
- We have to save them!
- Opal, get out of here!
We'll be fine!
Just go!
- I'll be back for you!
I love you!
- Zaofu is ours!
- Bring the citizens of zaofu
to kneel
Before the great uniter.
All who pledge their loyalty
to me
Will keep their freedom
and be dealt with fairly
As full citizens
of the earth empire.
The rest will be imprisoned
as traitors,
Like su beifong
and her sons.
Now bow.
Bow to her!
Do it!
She is your rightful leader!
- I'm so disappointed in you,
junior.
- Take them away!
- Get your hands off me.
You're crushing
my individuality.
- All hail the great uniter!
- Are you sure there's no way
they survived?
- Positive, but I think
I can replicate his work
With the spirit vines
and get us back on track.
I'll just need an assistant.
- How would you like
to help baatar build
The most powerful weapon
the world has ever seen?
- It would be my honor,
great uniter.
- Begin dismantling
the domes.