Earth.
Fire.
Air.
Water.
Only the Avatar can
master all four elements
and bring balance to the world.
Sync & corrections by wilson0804
www.Addic7ed.com
Kuvira has defeated the Avatar
and now controls the entire earth empire.
Luckily, the airbender
kids and Opal rescued Korra
and escaped Zaofu.
For the first time in three years,
Korra will finally be
back in Republic City.
Meanwhile, Varrick and
Bolin escaped from Baatar Jr.
And are on the run.
But will they make it
back to the city in time
to warn everyone about Kuvira's
new spirit energy super weapon?
Naga!
I missed you so much, girl.
Mom! Dad! We're back!
And we got Korra!
Well, aren't you a sight for sore eyes.
Bum-Ju and I sure missed you.
It's so great to see you again, Bumi.
And you too, Bum-Ju.
Well done, kids.
I'm proud of you all for finding Korra.
Proud enough to get me my tats?
No.
Welcome home.
I missed you, Tenzin.
Now, I hate to get right down to business,
but I want to hear what happened in Zaofu.
Way to ruin the moment.
Kuvira's whole army was there.
She captured mom, dad, and my brothers.
I thought I was strong enough to stop her.
I feel like such a failure.
No one expected you to
handle Kuvira on your own.
It's up to all of us to
find a way to deal with her.
We're just glad to have you back.
Where's Bolin?
He's not still on Kuvira's side, is he?
I can't believe he would stay with her
after what she did to my family.
But we don't know where he is.
How about you use your
own legs for a while?
You know, when I fled
Republic City with Zhu Li,
she carried me twenty Miles in one day.
And that was after she sprained her ankle.
Well, Zhu Li's not here, okay?
That's fine.
Leave me here. Let the worms gobble me up.
I deserve it. No way, mister.
You're not getting off that easily.
You're responsible for that
weapon Kuvira's trying to make.
Which, may I remind you,
could hurt a lot of people.
No, don't remind me!
I know, I'm a horrible, horrible person.
Okay, look,
Kuvira fooled us both
into doing her dirty work
and I'm not happy about it either.
But you know how we're gonna
make it up to the world?
By getting back to Republic City
and warning everyone what she's up to.
So I want you to take my hand,
and march with me out of this forest!
You really have a way with words, kid.
No wonder I made you a mover star.
All right, I'll take the
driver's seat for a while.
Hop on.
Great.
My feet could use a break.
Okay. Oh, boy.
Here we go.
- Ah!
- Oh!
Are you kidding me?
I hope you haven't been waiting long.
Only three years.
It's so good to see you again.
You too.
And I'm loving the hair.
Thanks. You're looking snazzy as always.
Come on, Mako got us a
table at the restaurant.
Korra!
Hi, Mako.
Hello there, Prince Wu,
rightful heir to the
throne, and this guy's boss.
I bet he's
told you a lot about me.
Nope. Not a thing.
Then we have so much to talk about.
You are going to love the food here.
I know the chef personally.
Let's start with a round of
your spicy octopus fritters.
And keep the cucumber-aloe water flowing.
Got to keep this princely skin hydrated.
I thought it was just
going to be the three of us.
Sorry, I couldn't ditch him.
But he promised to be on his best behavior.
Hey, pop into the Avatar state for me.
I want to see your eyes glow.
What? No.
So can you go into the Avatar state again?
I was worried when you
told me you couldn't.
Wait.
When did she tell you she couldn't?
What's going on with you two?
I wrote to Asami while I was away.
I asked her not to tell you. I'm sorry.
Well, why didn't you ever write to me?
Or Bolin?
I don't know.
I guess I didn't know what to say.
A "hello" would have been nice.
Mako, if it makes you feel any better,
she didn't write me either.
Why would she...
Never mind.
I'm sorry I didn't stay
in touch, but I'm back now.
And I want to know everything
about what's been going on with you two.
Well, I kind of have some big news.
I went to visit my
father for the first time.
He'd been writing me letters
and I guess I finally felt
ready to try and forgive him.
You sure you can trust him?
He might just be manipulating you again.
You think I don't know what
my own father is capable of?
No. No, I didn't mean...
you don't get to disappear for three years
and then act like you
know what's best for me.
It's not like I planned
to be gone that long.
I wanted to come back, but
I never felt ready until now.
As much as I'm enjoying
this little catch-up,
my royal bladder is about to explode.
Mako?
Come on, I need you to stand guard.
I'm not gonna hold your hand
every time you have to
empty your royal bladder.
Go to the bathroom on your own for once.
Fine.
Do you always go to the bathroom with him?
I don't go "with him" with him.
I just stand there in the
general vicinity while he...
I don't want to talk about it.
Good afternoon, sir.
Perhaps a spritz of cologne to freshen up?
Make it a double, buddy.
Mako, help!
Wu down.
Wu... Down.
I wish Pabu were here.
He could just chew us out of this.
You know who else has
incisors sharp as a knife?
Zhu Li.
Well, look what we caught.
Wonder if they were
tracking us after we escaped.
Hello, fellow travelers!
I don't suppose you could
help us out of this net?
Why would we free a couple of
lowly earth empire soldiers?
Lowly?
We were part of Kuvira's inner circle!
Were! Not anymore.
We jumped ship. Please just let us out.
I think I know just what to do
with a couple of Kuvira's top men.
Snap!
Ahh!
I wonder what's taking Wu so long.
He's not one to miss out on lunch.
I'll go check on him.
Wu, you in here?
Come on, your octopus
fritters are getting cold.
I'll be right back.
Excuse me, did you happen to see
if Prince Wu came out this way?
Sorry, miss. Haven't seen him.
Hmm. I'm in laundry.
Ah!
They've got Wu!
Get the car, I'm going after them.
Get in.
- Ah!
We're losing them.
Hang a right at the next block.
We can cut them off on seventh.
You missed the turn! Where are you going?
I know these streets better than you.
I built some of them.
What are you doing? Sit down.
Where is he?
Whoa!
Wu's not here.
This guy was the only one in the truck.
Where's the prince?
Halfway to Kuvira by now.
All hail the Great Uniter.
They must have moved Wu
to a different vehicle
when we lost sight of them.
Take this guy in for booking.
Charge him with kidnapping.
And tell Chief Beifong
that Prince Wu is missing.
Put out an all points bulletin.
We'll keep looking.
Where do we start?
There are thousands of cars in the city
and he could be in any one of them.
Or they might try smuggling
him out on an airship.
Or maybe a boat.
He could be anywhere!
The one time I don't watch him
pee and this is what happens.
They're taking Wu to the train station!
Are you sure? How do you know?
I'll explain on the way, just drive!
We're running out of time!
So how did a bunch of
water and fire benders
end up in one of Kuvira's
reeducation camps?
Call it what it is... a prison.
Kuvira's been purging states of anyone
who's not of earth kingdom
origin and locking them up.
Purging?
What are you acting so surprised for?
You must have known what she was up to,
being part of her "inner circle" and all.
No, I swear.
And the inner circle thing
lasted, like, less than a day.
Will you at least tell
us where you're taking us?
The border checkpoint.
You're gonna help us talk our way past
some earth empire soldiers.
And once we're through,
we'll see about letting you go.
Ha ha!
Lava time! Bet you didn't expect that!
Look, I'm sorry for what
happened to all of you,
but as I've been trying to explain,
we don't work for Kuvira anymore.
Yeah, if our handsome mugs get recognized
trying to go through that checkpoint,
we're goners!
If you really are fugitives,
you better listen up.
We've been scouting this region for days.
There's a wall stretching
along the entire border
and patrols guarding every part of it.
That checkpoint is our only way out.
It's not worth the risk, baraz.
How do we know they won't turn us in?
If he wanted us gone,
we'd be at the bottom of
a pool of lava right now.
If any of us want to get out
of the earth empire alive,
we'll have to trust each other.
All right, where's this checkpoint?
So how do you know where Wu is
just by touching some spirit vines?
I learned how to connect to
people's energy through them.
Who taught you that?
Lin's mom.
I found her in the swamp.
That place is like one giant spirit wild.
You met Toph?
What was she like?
A cranky, more miserable version of Lin.
Is that even possible?
You'd be surprised.
Which train is Wu on?
I don't know!
Split up and start looking.
Follow my lead.
Good afternoon, sir. Can we help you?
You sure can.
We captured these escaped prisoners.
We need to get them to a secure facility.
- Where'd they escape from?
- Camp 14.
Then why are you bringing them through here?
Camp 14's back the other way.
You think we don't know where camp 14 is?
Kuvira wants them transferred.
Then I'll need to see the transfer order.
Listen, pal, I had to
fight off 2 badger-moles,
6 wolf-bats, and 18
hog-monkeys to get these guys.
So sorry if I don't have the paperwork.
I was too busy cramming
it in a hog-monkey's mouth
while it was trying to eat me.
I am in sore need of a shower
and I have blisters that
are the size of cantaloupes
and twice as juicy!
So you can let us through,
or you can give me your name and rank
and I'll pass it on to Kuvira.
You know what happens to soldiers
who question her orders, don't you?
Bad stuff!
Let them through!
Wait! Stop them!
They're traitors to the empire!
There's no way I'm going back to prison!
Ah. Ah! Ah!
Ah!
Boy, I sure hope this works.
I still got that Varrick touch.
We're clear. Come on!
Ah!
Varrick, wait! We can't leave them.
Retreat!
Thanks. You didn't have to come back.
Yeah, I kind of did.
Let's go.
The 4:15 bound for Omashu
is now leaving on track number six.
All aboard!
If we don't find Wu soon,
we might never find him.
He's on that train!
How do you know for sure he's here?
I don't. But I had a feeling, okay?
And I'm just supposed to
trust "Avatar feelings"?
You wouldn't have to if
you had guarded the prince
like you were supposed to.
Oh, so it's my fault Wu disappeared.
It's certainly not mine!
Guys, shh.
Listen.
Wu! Wu, it's me.
Mako? Where am I?
Am I dead? No, you're on a train.
We're gonna get you out of here.
- Gah!
- Ah!
Everyone out.
I'm not going up there.
Ah!
Jump!
- Ah!
- You all right?
- Yes!
Thank you, thank you, thank you,
thank you, thank you, thank you,
thank you, thank you, thank you.
You are definitely getting a raise, buddy.
You should be thanking Korra.
We never would have found you without her.
I owe you my life, Avatar.
If only there was some way to repay you.
Ooh, I know.
How about I take you out
for a night on the town?
Really? You're asking me out right now?
So... I'll put you down for a "maybe"?
How about a never?
Not exactly what I imagined
for our first day back together.
But it was kind of like old times.
Except for the getting on
each other's nerves part.
Actually, that is like
old times for me and Korra.
I'm sorry things got so tense earlier.
It's all right.
I guess after being apart for three years,
there's bound to be a bit
of an adjustment period.
Yeah, but it's great to have you back.
There's no place else I'd rather be.
Mm.
You guys are the greatest
friends a guy could have.
So what are we gonna do with him?
It's too dangerous to
take him back to the hotel.
Whoo. You're telling me!
I need a cushy safe house somewhere.
I think I know just the place.
Nice digs, Mako.
You didn't tell me you came from money.
I don't. This is Asami's place.
She was nice enough to
let my family stay here
after they fled Ba Sing Se.
Mako!
It's so wonderful to...
Are you...
Grandma, this is Prince Wu.
He needs to stay with you and
the family for a little while.
It's an honor, grandma Mako.
She loves royalty.
I think I'll fit right in here.
Thanks for looking out for me, Mako.
Now where's the nearest bathroom?
I have been holding it all day!
I know it might not mean much
coming from a guy wearing this uniform,
but I'd like to apologize for
what Kuvira's put you through.
I appreciate that.
Guess this is where we part ways.
It's been a blast!
We're heading north too.
Why don't you come with us?
It's the least we can do
after you saved our necks.
On that hunk of junk? No thanks.
I'm allergic to drowning.
Oof!
I mean, uh, we'd love a lift!
Ew. Uh.
This area is overrun with spirit vines
and they appear to be even more powerful
than the samples we
took from Republic City.
Perfect.
Harvest these vines until
there's nothing left.
Sync & corrections by wilson0804
www.Addic7ed.com