Earth.
Fire.
Air.
Water.
Only the Avatar can
master all four elements
and bring balance to the world.
Sync & corrections by wilson0804
www.Addic7ed.com
Avatar Korra is back and
yours truly, Shiro Shinobi,
couldn't be more thrilled.
It's been my honor to bring you news
of Korra and her friends over the years.
So many heart-pounding moments!
Who can forget Amon and
his Equalist revolution?
I still have nightmares!
Then there was that time
I covered the Nuktuk mover premiere.
Boy, was that fun. But enough about me.
Sit back, relax, and take
a trip down memory lane.
__
You know, there's something
about being kidnapped
that makes a guy realize he
needs to get his act together.
Yeah, I agree.
Let's toughen you up.
Ahh! I wasn't ready!
Wu down!
What's going on?
Mako, how dare you injure the prince?
Would his royal highness
like a cherry-Berry lemonade?
And maybe some of those
sticky dumplings too?
Look at you.
You're so weak, "Wu
down" is your catchphrase.
I know, I'm a wimp.
But it's not my fault. I was born that way.
I'm not like you, Mako.
I wasn't raised by a
pack of cops in the woods.
You don't know anything about me, do you?
Yeah, I'm drawing a blank. Why is that?
How do I not know stuff about you?
Uh... You never asked?
Well, I'm asking now.
What's your favorite food?
What's your favorite color?
Is there a special lady in your life?
Not since Korra and I broke up.
What? You dated the Avatar? Sit.
You and I need to have a
little gab session right now.
How'd you guys first meet?
Bolin and I were playing
for the fire ferrets.
You were a pro-bender?
Yes.
Will you just let me tell the story?
Carry on.
Bolin and I grew up dirt poor,
so once I became a
pro-bender, I wanted it all:
Riches, fame, accolades.
But all that changed when I met Korra.
Come here. I want you meet my brother,
Mako.
Mako?
Wow, I heard you play on the radio.
Come on, Bolin, we're up.
Whoa, that was the first time you met?
Kind of rude there, buddy.
Know what else is rude? Interrupting.
Korra proved to be an amazing pro-bender,
and a loyal friend.
She helped me save Bolin when
he was taken by the Equalists.
After going through
such a crazy experience,
I felt like Korra and I
had a powerful connection.
So then you smooched her real good?
Huh? Huh?
Not exactly.
Ah!
Oh, no. I'm so sorry.
I didn't see you.
How could you not see me?
I mean, I was ju...
I was... I-I... wow.
That was...
Wait.
That was the first thing you said to Asami?
You really got to work
on your introductions.
Hey, when you got charm like mine,
you don't need introductions.
Hanging out with Asami was awesome,
but it made things with
Korra... Complicated.
So I was thinking we should
spend some time together.
Look, I really like you
and I think we were meant for each other.
Korra, I'm really sorry but...
I just don't feel the same way about you.
That's harsh, Mako.
I know, and the worst part about it is,
it wasn't totally true.
We need to talk.
Save your breath.
You've already made it
clear how you feel about me.
No, I haven't.
What I'm trying to say is...
As much as you drive me crazy,
I also think you're pretty amazing.
Hot dog!
Smooch city here we come.
You player.
Whoa.
I thought you were dating Asami.
Tu, get out of here!
Naughty Mako. You take
after your grandfather.
Guys, grandma,
everything wasn't so cut and dry.
I wasn't dating Asami.
Denial.
Okay, maybe I was dating her.
It was all very confusing.
But my feelings for Korra became
clear when Tarrlok captured her.
It felt like a piece of me was gone.
I was so worried.
Are you all right?
I'm fine.
I'm glad you're here.
Oof.
I bet Asami wasn't too happy about that.
I've noticed how you treat Korra...
How you acted when she was missing.
You have feelings for her, don't you?
Things are crazy right now.
Can we deal with our
relationship problems later?
Well, there might not be any relationship
to worry about later.
Asami!
Ouch.
Yup. Turns out she was right.
It was time to man up and call it quits.
Asami,
I'm sorry things got
so messed up between us.
But whatever happens today,
I want you to know how
much I care about you.
I care about you too.
Wait, was that supposed to
be you breaking up with her?
Yes. That was a breakup.
Didn't sound like a breakup.
It was mutual. We had an understanding.
We both knew...
can I just get on with the
rest of my story or what?
Fine.
But I hope you weren't
as ambiguous with Korra
as you were with Asami.
Trust me, I wasn't.
Korra and I ended up stopping Amon together
and after that, I was finally
able to tell her how I felt.
Exactly how I felt.
I love you, Korra.
I love you too.
Aww.
And then you two lived happily ever after?
Um...
Tenzin's just trying to help you
become the best Avatar you can be.
Of course you take his side.
I'm not taking his side.
You know, sometimes I
wonder whose side you're on.
There aren't any sides!
How could you take his side?
What's with you and sides?
Well, excuse me, officer!
Don't let me stand in the
way of you writing tickets.
I'm just trying to save the world!
Well, I guess that if we're
both putting our jobs first,
maybe there's no room for our relationship.
So what?
Are you breaking up with me?
Yeah. I guess I am.
Now that's a breakup!
After that, I dove into my work.
Someone had been taking out supply ships
heading to the Southern water tribe.
Asami's company was one of the victims,
so she and I worked
together to catch the perps.
The stakeout was the perfect
way to get my mind off Korra.
It was an intense night.
Asami and I discovered the
triads had double crossed us.
We barely got away,
but by then Asami's warehouse
had been cleared out.
My company... It's over.
I give up.
Well, I'm not giving up on you.
I know, I know. Don't tell me.
I had no right kissing Asami.
No, actually, I'm
completely fine with that.
You officially broke up with Korra
and therefore, you're free
to smooch whoever you wish.
If only it had been that simple.
Mako, I missed you so much!
Korra, hey, I missed you too.
So you're not still mad at me?
We had that fight before
you left, remember?
Not really.
I got attacked by a dark spirit
and I lost my memory for a little while.
Maybe it hasn't all come back yet.
Was it a bad fight?
Ahh...
Hmm... No.
No. It wasn't that bad.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
So you were back with Asami,
but then Korra came back
and thought you guys were still together
and you didn't tell her you weren't?
Just like your grandfather.
Well, me and Asami were never
officially back together.
Really? That again?
You know, it seems like you're
so afraid to disappoint anyone
that you end up disappointing everyone.
Truer words have never been spoken.
High five!
Well, eventually, I did tell Korra
but by then she already knew.
Why didn't you just tell me
the truth in the first place?
I know I should have, but...
I didn't want to hurt you all over again.
I guess part of me wanted to
forget about the breakup too.
I think we both know that this...
Us... Doesn't work.
You're right.
It's over.
For real this time.
After harmonic convergence,
the world changed.
Team Avatar traveled around
searching for new airbenders.
At first, it was awkward
being around Korra and Asami.
As you were.
Ladies.
But then I realized I
had to realize who I was
without a lady in my life.
I know what that's like.
I mean, to need distance from women,
because I have so many all over me,
all the time.
Anyway,
I eventually helped Korra defeat Zaheer
and save the airbenders
and we did it as friends.
Korra showed me the importance
of putting others before myself.
And whenever I think of her,
she continues to inspire me.
Wow.
That story is amazing
and I really learned something.
You did? Good.
Yeah, I learned that I really
didn't know anything about you.
Crazy!
Also, I realized that
ladies are complicated.
No offense, grandma.
None taken.
I better just focus on being a better king.
Okay, come at me.
I can take it.
Ah! Wu down!
I brought you some tea.
I thought you might be cold out here.
You're so sweet.
Thanks.
Are you okay?
You seem out of sorts.
Sorry.
I've just been thinking
about something Toph said.
She told me that the world doesn't need me
and it's basically pointless
to try to stop Kuvira.
That's ridiculous.
At the time, I thought so too.
I figured she was just being
her normal, cranky self,
but I'm beginning to think she had a point.
No, she doesn't.
The world does need you.
You're the Avatar.
But no matter what I do,
the world seems to
always be out of balance.
Growing up, I couldn't
wait to be the Avatar.
I thought I was really gonna change things.
I was so naive.
The first time I saw Amon
take someone's bending away,
I was terrified.
Your firebending is gone.
Forever.
Then my worst nightmare came true.
Korra!
No!
I told you I would destroy you.
Korra, you're forgetting about
all the good that happened
after you exposed Amon as the fraud he was.
The Equalist movement lost
its leader and its power.
Free elections were held
in the united Republic
and non-benders finally had a voice.
People had hope again and
it was all because of you.
And I was hopeful too.
But that feeling didn't last long.
As soon as I defeated Amon,
a new enemy took his place.
I can't I trusted you.
You made me think you
wanted to restore balance
with the spirits, but
this... this isn't balance.
It's madness!
Now let her go.
If you want your friend to
make it out of the spirit world,
you'll open the other portal now.
Because of Unalaq, I betrayed Tenzin,
opened the portals,
and threw the spirit and
human worlds into chaos.
It was my fault he fused with
Vaatu and became a dark Avatar.
And I was helpless to stop
him from destroying Raava
and cutting off my
connection to my past lives.
With Raava gone,
Unalaq and Vaatu became
more powerful than ever.
But you became more powerful too.
I mean, you turned into a giant spirit.
Yeah, that was pretty awesome.
And opening the spirit portals
turned out to be a good thing.
You brought back the airbenders
and cause a positive shift in the world.
Yes, but Zaheer got airbending too,
and nearly killed me.
If it weren't for Zaheer,
the earth queen would still be alive.
There would have been no
crisis in the earth kingdom,
and Kuvira wouldn't be in power.
Things are more out of
balance than ever now.
Nothing's changed!
You're right, Korra.
I am?
She is?
It's true, there will
always be new conflicts
and enemies to face.
But the important thing is
to learn from your enemies
and better yourself over
time, which you have.
You've changed so much
since you first arrived
on air temple island.
When you first came
here, you were hotheaded
and a bit selfish.
But you've matured into
a thoughtful young woman
who puts the needs of
others before herself.
The new air nation is a testament to that.
You sacrificed everything to save them.
You're an inspiration to the world.
Thank you both.
I know that this Kuvira problem
is only going to get worse.
But no matter what happens,
no matter how crazy things get,
I'll always try to restore balance.
And that's when I made a solemn vow
never to eat bark-onion soup again.
Been six years, four months, and 14 days...
ugh. I can still taste it.
Does anyone else feel like
throwing themselves overboard?
Not me!
I've spent the last few hours tuning out
all these incredibly boring stories...
Hey!
All the while mentally composing
the most exciting tale ever told,
soon become the greatest mover ever made!
I present to you now:
Bolin, as Nuktuk, here of the South...
trademark Varrimovers International...
in the incredible true story of Bolin!
Hero of the world!
Wait, am I playing Nuktuk,
or is Nuktuk playing me?
Both.
It's your true story, but we'll capitalize
on the audience of the Nuktuk franchise.
Duh.
How can you call me the hero of the world?
I left my friends and family
to join up with a psychotic
dictator who imprisoned me,
and now I'm running back home
with my tail between my legs.
Nya, Ba, Ba, Ba, Ba.
You're emphasizing the wrong story beats.
Let me tell it.
The story of Bolin
begins in an exotic port of call.
A wise sage, the richest
merchant in the world,
and a handsome devil all
sit on a single pillow
in the living room of a luxury yacht.
How do they all fit on one pillow?
Ooh! Giant pillow!
Wrong!
They're all the same man! Me!
I try to teach a swami
the power of levitation,
but he's too stupid to understand it,
so I kick him out.
"Upon whom can I bestow
my awesome knowledge?"
I ask myself.
Then in walks Nuktuk
with a twinkle in his eye,
a gorgeous dame on his
arm, and a song on his lips.
He bursts into a rapturous melody...
♪ Where can I find my teacher? ♪
Oh, come on!
I wasn't singing, you were not levitating.
And Asami is just a
friend, thank you very much.
If you want to tell my true story,
you should start from when I met Korra.
She came to the bending
arena one fateful night...
This place is even more
amazing than I imagined!
Name's Bolin, by the way.
Korra.
Boring!
When does the singing start?
There wasn't any singing.
Boo!
You're onscreen talent, kid.
Leave the storytelling to the masters.
So the trouble begins when the Avatar
is trapped in the spirit world.
The world's most evil villains realize
that with Korra out of the way,
the time is right to try to take out Bolin.
So the worst of the worst team up.
They're led by Zaheer...
leader of red lotus
and master of the skies!
A flying chaotic chaos machine!
He's joined by Vaatu...
the ultimate force of pure
spirit evil in the universe!
The biggest, meanest,
scariest kite that ever flew!
Wait, Zaheer didn't team up with Vaatu.
How would that even happen?
How do you think?
Hello?
Hey, it's Zaheer.
Oh, hey, Zaheer.
Glad I caught you at home.
Uh-huh. Very funny.
Like I can leave this stupid tree.
Hold on. Let me conference in...
Amon!
The reanimated zombie body
of the bloodbending
leader of the Equalists!
Hey, guys, I'm totally
in for taking out Bolin.
He's way too powerful and awesome.
But can we please not include...
not include who, Amon?
The evil Unalaq,
the diabolical but incredibly
boring and unpopular sorcerer
from the north, who's
listening in on the other line!
I've spent my life trying to defeat Nuktuk,
I mean, Bolin,
and I know just where to find him...
with all the beautiful ladies.
Yes, Bolin had a reputation
as the world's greatest ladies' man.
Ooh, now the story's getting interesting.
After leaving the beautiful
but emotionally unstable
water tribe princess at the altar,
he met a fetching airbender,
the heir to a vast earth kingdom fortune.
Opal, so smart and caring.
So pretty to smell...
And she'll probably never talk to me again
because I'm so stupid!
Stupid!
So, so, so stupid!
Pull it together, you leaky lug.
But the darkest moment is
always right before the dawn.
For at his lowest point,
Bolin sought advice from
the man who started it all,
the wisest of the wise... me!
For some of my signature sage advice!
Nuktuk, I mean, Bolin,
there's only one thing for you to do
if you want to save the Avatar
and defeat the fearsome foursome.
I'm not really sure if I like "fearsome."
I mean, evil squared might be better.
Whatever.
You have to assemble the
fightingest airbender army
of all time!
But it turns out the airbender
recruits are a sorry lot,
so Bolin brings them to a secret
mountaintop training facility
where he teaches them the
ancient art of dodging fruit
and balancing on sticks!
Meanwhile, back with zombie Amon...
Okay, guys, I think we finally ditched him.
Ha ha. Very funny.
I'm still on the line.
So about that evil plan
to destroy Nuktuk...
Hello? Anyone there?
Guys!
And with danger closing in, Opal realizes
how much she loves Bolin and forgives him
for whatever stuff he
was talking about earlier
which will probably not be in the final cut
of the mover anyway.
She does?
Aww.
And she kisses Bolin,
magically passing on the
airbender power of flight!
Okay, that part seems
a little unbelievable.
This is no time for thinking, kid.
We're heading into the big finale!
Bolin gathers his airbender army
to fight alongside Rotan and Juji
against the Terror Square!
Maybe that's the name of the bad guys...
Terror Square. What
about legion of darkness?
Well, we'll put a focus group on it.
Bolin teaches the airbenders
to create a giant tornado.
Then he flies around in the sky,
pushes Zaheer into it,
turning him into wind forever!
But Bolin doesn't realize that
the universal interplanetary
combination zero hour...
talk about a ticking clock...
is almost upon him!
And when Juji shoots his
laser eyes at the evil Unalaq,
the beams accidentally fly
into the magic spirit doorway!
They bounce off Vaatu, setting him free,
and hit Bolin, turning him into a giant!
But when Vaatu is set
free, the evil Unalaq,
who has always been an
annoyingly clingy person,
is so close to Vaatu that they combine
into one horrifying monster!
Giant Bolin and the evil Unavaatu fight
toe-to-toe, zapping each
other with their laser beams
as they stomp around Republic City.
It looks like the evil Unavaatu might win,
but thankfully, Bolin's spiritual mojo
is so strong that he attracts
the queen of the fairies!
With her help, Bolin turns
Unavaatu into magic dust
and sprays him into the sky.
And that's where the stars come from.
Oh, yeah, and he turns into a dragon,
and he goes into the spirit
world and saves the Avatar.
The end!
Wait. You like that?
It didn't make any sense!
What about zombie Amon?
What happened to him, huh?
And-and-and-and stars
are magic fairy dust?
Are you guys crazy? Are you crazy?
It's just a mover. Don't overthink it.
It's like a ride.
Never let the truth
get in the way of a good story, kid.
Sync & corrections by wilson0804
www.Addic7ed.com